<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OzoneOC</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on OzoneOC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© Ozone 2023</copyright><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>/aboutme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/aboutme/</guid><description>
Specs # Main Rig # 12700K @ 5.1GHz core/4.8GHz ring (HT and E cores off) + Heatkiller IV PRO 2x8GB G.Skill ARES (3200c14-14-14-34) @ 4000c15-16-15-39 2T w/ 120mm mem fan MSI PRO Z690-A DDR4 Gigabyte Xtreme Gaming GTX1080 deshroud + 2x 120mm fans @ 2000MHz core/5400MHz VRAM MX500 500GB M.2 SN550 500GB Toshiba P300 2TB Fractal Pop Air XL MSI A750GF Custom loop: 2x 280mm Corsair XR5 (2x NB ELOOP-X 140mm ARGB + 2x P14 push/pull front, 2x Kaze Flex 140mm RGB top), EK XRES-140 DDC, EK ZMT 16/10mm matte black soft tubing, XSPC G1/4 16/10mm compression fittings Testbench # LD PC-V2 single stage phase change (-50°C evap head) Motherboards: Asus Maximus V Gene Asus Crosshair IV Formula Asus P5B Deluxe (voltmodded) Gigabyte GA-970A-D3 Memory: G.</description></item><item><title>Fans</title><link>/resources/fans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resources/fans/</guid><description>
Table of Contents # Information Static Pressure Bearings Non-RGB Fans 120mm 140mm 40mm 80-92mm 180mm RGB Fans 120mm RGB 140mm RGB Information # Static Pressure # Static pressure is the amount of pressure exerted in the direction of the fan is pushing the air, which will help it with cooling in situations with restrictive airflow, such as radiators. This will make fans that are optimised for static pressure perform better on radiators compared to ones that aren&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item><item><title>Graphics Cards</title><link>/resources/graphics-cards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resources/graphics-cards/</guid><description>
Table of Contents # Benchmarks Overclocking Benchmarks # TechPowerUp GPU Reviews # Tom&amp;rsquo;s Hardware GPU Heirarchy # Overclocking # Software # MSI Afterburner # Benchmarks/Stress Tests # 3DMark # Use timespy to measure performance Set a looped custom run to stress test GPU overclock</description></item><item><title>Memory</title><link>/resources/memory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resources/memory/</guid><description>
Table of Contents # Basics ICs DDR5 ICs DDR4 ICs Overclocking Guides Stress Tests Alderlake DDR4 Overclocking Zen2 DDR4 Overclocking Zen DDR4 Overclocking Lantency In-Depth tRAS tRC First Word Latency Basics # Understanding Frequency and Timings # DDR4 Memory Gear-Down Mode Explained # ICs # DDR5 ICs # DDR5 IC Tier List # Tier ICs Description S Hynix A-Die Best DDR5 IC known (however, worse than M-Die on Zen4). A Hynix M-Die High performing IC, can still be overclocked very far.</description></item><item><title>Motherboards</title><link>/resources/motherboards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resources/motherboards/</guid><description>
Table of Contents # VRMs VRM Basics VRM Charts Best Overlocking Motherboards Intel Consumer Boards VRMs # Explanation # VRM Basics # How VRMs Work # VRM Charts # Z690 &amp;amp; Z790 VRM Chart # LGA1200 VRM Chart # AM4 VRM Chart # Best Overclocking Motherboards # Intel Consumer Boards # Chipset Board Z68 Maximus IV Extreme, Maximus IV Gene Z77 Maximus V Formula, Maximus V Gene Z87 Z87 OC Formula, Maximus VI Gene Z97 Z97X-SOC-FORCE-LN2 (whole Z97X-SOC series is fine), Maximus VII Gene Z170 Z170M OC Formula Z270 Maximus IX Apex Z390 Maximus XI Apex, Maximus XI Gene Z490 Maximus XII Apex, Z490 Dark Kingpin, Z490 Unify ITX Z590 Maximus XIII Apex, Z590 Tachyon Z690 Z690 Apex, Z690 Dark Kingpin, Z690 Unify ITX Z790 Z790 Apex, Z790 Edge ITX</description></item><item><title>Processors</title><link>/resources/processors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resources/processors/</guid><description>
Table of Contents # Benchmarks Binning Overclocking Intel Microarchitecture Alderlake Skylake AMD Microarchitecture Zen4 Zen3 Zen2 Benchmarks: # TechPowerUp CPU Reviews # Tom&amp;rsquo;s Hardware CPU Reviews # Binning # Silicon Lottery Historical Binning Statistics # Ivylake Batch Numbers # Overclocking # Stress Tests # prime95 # Run application at small FFT AVX2 torture test for 1-2 hours to achieve maximum stability. If you&amp;rsquo;re not bothered about being as stable as possible but just want very strong stability, run application at small FFT without AVX torture test for 1-2 hours.</description></item></channel></rss>