<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OzoneOC</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on OzoneOC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/122055209?s=200&amp;v=4"/>
This site is used for storing information, and benchmarks about hardware, and is aimed to be useful for hardware enthusiasts or people new to PCs who want to learn more.
Discord: Ozone#6539 # My HWBot Profile #</description></item><item><title>Alderlake DDR4 Memory Overclocking</title><link>/posts/overclocking/alderlake-ddr4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/overclocking/alderlake-ddr4/</guid><description>
These notes are for memory overclocking Samsung B-Die on chips such as the 12700K or 12900K; higher end unlocked Alderlake chips with better IMCs.
This is not a guide on how to overclock memory, it&amp;rsquo;s only notes exclusive to Alderlake as it can be trickier than normal. If you want to learn how to OC memory, read the MemTestHelper DDR4 OC Guide by by integralfx.
Hardware # CPU # Good CPUs for memory overclocking consist of the 12700K, 12900K, and 12900KS.</description></item><item><title>Custom Watercooling</title><link>/posts/cooling/custom-watercooling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/cooling/custom-watercooling/</guid><description>
Custom watercooling is a high level form of watercooling usually used to cool components that draw a significant amount of power while getting very warm. This usually consists of cooling your CPU or GPU (or both, obviously), but people have also cooled their memory or even storage.
Parts # Waterblocks # These are mounted to the component desired to cool with fittings attatched to connect the tubing to it, in order to connect it to the rest of the loop.</description></item><item><title>Fans</title><link>/posts/cooling/fans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/cooling/fans/</guid><description>
Case fans are more important than people believe they are and can tend to make a notable difference in thermal performance
Information # Static Pressure # Static pressure is the amount of pressure exerted in the direction of the fan is pushing the air, which will help it with cooling in situations with restrictive airflow, such as radiators. This will make fans that are optimised for static pressure perform better on radiators compared to ones that aren&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item></channel></rss>